https://www.levitt-safety.com/privacy-policy/

Roof Guardrails
Self-Retracting Lifelines (SRL)
Multi Gas Detectors
Photoionization Detector (PID)
Dust & Particulate Monitoring
Particles Plus AQM Series Remote Particle Counter & Environmental Monitor
Gemini™ Handheld Analyzer
Indoor Air Quality (IAQ)
Chemical Splash
Electrocardiograms (ECGs)
IoT Safety Solutions
Lockout/Tagout (LOTO)
Air Carts, Compressors & Air Filtration Systems
Air-Purifying Respirators (APRs)
Breathing Air Compressors
Powered Air Purifying Respirators (PAPRs)
Back
Powered Air Purifying Respirators (PAPRs)
CleanSpace® Family of Powered Air Purifying Respirators (PAPR)
AccuFIT9000™ Quantitative Respirator Fit Tester
Self-Contained Breathing Apparatus (SCBA)
Supplied Air Respirators (SARs)
iNet® Solutions
Learning Management System (LMS)
Online Courses
WorkStyle Profiling
Vehicle Fire Suppression Systems
Back
All Vehicle Fire Suppression Systems (VFSS)
Fixed Gas Detection
Occupational Health & Industrial Hygiene Instrument Calibration
Noise Assessments
Indoor Air Quality (IAQ)
Hearing Conservation
Indoor Air Quality (IAQ)
Confined Space for Supervisors Training
Confined Space Rescue Industry Training (Non-IDLH)
Dentistry
Fire Departments & Emergency Services (EMS)
iNet® Solutions
Learning Management System (LMS)
Search
Levitt-Safety is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and is committed to protecting your privacy and providing you with a safe online experience. When you browse the Site, you do so anonymously. You can visit Levitt-Safety.com without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when Levitt-Safety may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name and address. Usually, this information is used only to respond to your inquiry, process an order or allow you to access specific account information. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that may be automatically collected by Levitt-Safety and may be shared with other web sites within the Levitt-Safety family of web sites. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. This information is used by Levitt-Safety for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Site.
Levitt-Safety may collect and use your personal information to operate the Site and deliver the services you have requested. We may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Levitt-Safety and its affiliates. Levitt-Safety keeps track of the web sites and pages our customers visit within the Site, in order to determine what web sites, web pages and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Levitt-Safety to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
We will not disclose your personal information, without notice, unless we are required to do so by law or we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to 1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Levitt-Safety or the Site; 2) protect and defend the rights or property of Levitt-Safety or its affiliated companies; 3) enforce these Terms and Conditions; 4) protect the personal safety of users of Levitt-Safety, the Site, or the public; and, 5) as otherwise indicated in these Terms and Conditions.
Levitt-Safety encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to from Levitt-Safety so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. Levitt-Safety is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on web sites outside of the Levitt-Safety and Levitt-Safety family of web sites.
For further information or inquires, you may contact us.
Looking for help?
Send Us Feedback
Subscribe
What can we help you with?
Comments
Send Us Feedback
How likely are you to make a purchase from Levitt-Safety website in the future? *
Please Select...
How likely are you to recommend Levitt-Safety to someone else? *
Please Select...
Please Select...
